This is my first git project add more

Whether it be rumours, counter-rumours, new contracts or the all-important done deals, you will find it here. Whether it be rumours, counter-rumours, new contracts or the all-important done deals, you will find it here. Whether it be rumours, counter-rumours, new contracts or the all-important done deals, you will find it here. Whether it be rumours, counter-rumours, new. 

Whether it be rumours, counter-rumours, new contracts or the all-important done deals, you will find it here. Whether it be rumours, counter-rumours, new contracts or the all-important done deals, you will find it here. Whether it be rumours, counter-rumours, new contracts or the all-important done deals, you will find it here. Whether it be rumours, counter-rumours, new. 